Hello welcome to the channel, I have come to
meet you and I wanted to tell you that a
fraud happened with me recently and
it could be a fraud with me or there is such a
thing which exists
in this world and people can fool someone in this way,
I had never thought of this,
I have heard a lot of frauds, I
mean every day people tell
about online frauds, many times people tell about
their different experiences about what
happened to them, how people
fooled them in front of their eyes or many times
people tell about the frauds that happened to
them online, but this was such a
fraud which was actually not an online fraud
and this was not such a fraud in
which you were fooled by a person standing in front of you,
so you will think that
when this was not such a fraud and it was not such a
fraud, it was not such a fraud,
then what kind of fraud was this, so this was a
third type of fraud and this has never happened
in life, but this time  When it happened,
I said I must share it with you
because after this fraud I was a
little disturbed for a day or two, so I
said that you guys might have had such a thing
because the fraud that happened to me was a very
common thing and generally such things that happen to people, such
incidents that happen to them are very common
because the
product due to which the fraud happened was one that we all use.
I am Sir,
in today's date I don't think that people would not
buy something like health insurance because health insurance is
such a thing which is
more important than life insurance because
even you do not know what will happen after you die,
you cannot see what will happen to your loved ones after you die and you cannot do anything
but you should not face any problem during your lifetime, that is why
you buy health insurance,
you think that if God forbid
you ever get any disease or you have to be
hospitalized, then in such a situation the
hospital bills are so high that it
seems that if the hospital bills have become so
high then how will we manage it, so that
people  Generally,
going to the hospital means that if there is
something like health insurance,
everyone uses it in their life. And God
forbid, if someone ever goes to a hospital, then the
problem in that case is that
people get more worried about the hospital bills than their illness. When the
bill
comes, what kind of bail will they get when they are discharged,
and what condition will they be in
if they get sick and
go to the hospital. Even mentioning the name of the hospital,
people took
health insurance to protect themselves
and I think this health insurance has been done
now, at least
six or seven years ago. When I bought it,
it was under the name Max Bupa. Today,
it has been changed and Nova has been booked in place of Max Bupa.
So when the
time came to renew the insurance, I started getting a lot of
marketing calls. So many
marketing calls that you will get upset.
Now people are calling you forcefully and
telling you about their policies, saying
that you should switch, don't
go to this one, buy another policy, it has
lower premiums and more benefits.  It has
more coverage, so after doing this I started getting a lot of
calls, so I thought that
my premium is
around Rs. 3000, my
annual premium for health insurance,
so when people call you, you listen to one or two of them
and they
also tell you why your health
insurance is
bad and why ours is good, so I started getting
calls from two-three companies,
Star Health Insurance, and
apart from that I started getting calls from Rally Jail as
well, and the most surprising
thing was when I got a call
from Novopa, and the people from Nova Bupa called me and
said that
under the latest update that we have done,
your premium will be ₹35000
and your critical illness cover will be
covered after the next 2 years from today, I was
so shocked that the point of critical illness,
I had already got it
after the initial gap of 2 years, so
suddenly the company not only  Not only did they not only
discontinue the policy but also increased the premium from Rs 30 to Rs
35 and I got so angry
and I immediately said that I do
not want to continue this policy, I will port it
and
take this policy from some other insurance company through court and after that
I disconnected the phone, after that I
remained in a state of shock for 2 days thinking how can this happen
and if I port it then
maybe that company too will not give me critical illness
cover, then what will happen, what will happen to the
premium that I have paid for the policy for so many years, what happened, I will
tell you further in my next video.